<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>radokristof on</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/contributors/radokristof/</link><description>Recent content in radokristof on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2021 18:50:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nrchkb.github.io/contributors/radokristof/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Quick Start</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/quick-start/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/quick-start/</guid><description>This wiki will be used to share examples so that users may see how this plugin functions and get started more easily with copyable flows for each HomeKit service. This page will assume you are familiar with Node-RED basics.
For new users, please start with the official Node-RED docs before continuing.
Nodes A Node is the basic building block of a flow. Nodes are triggered by either receiving a message from the previous node in a flow, or by waiting for some external event, such as change state of the light or some automated logic.</description></item><item><title>Characteristics</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/characteristics/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/characteristics/</guid><description>Characteristics are the values sent to the service item. They are generally true/false or number values. All services have at least one required characteristic. For example the switch has only the required characteristic of On.
Characteristic Properties The HomeKit service node has a section called &amp;ldquo;Characteristic Properties&amp;rdquo;. This section is used to define limits or initialize which characteristics you may send to your specific item.
The characteristic properties do not set any value in the item, instead they tell HomeKit that the item will be using that characteristic and define limits on the valid values.</description></item><item><title>Security System</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/service/security-system/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2021 18:50:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/service/security-system/</guid><description>Example This example uses node-red-contrib-alarm as an &amp;ldquo;alarm panel&amp;rdquo;. Many thanks for the devs over there!
The most basic parts are triggers going into alarm nodes and state changes coming to/from HomeKit. I have added in some handling of arming and disarming based on who is home and time of day (automatic arming at night or when we leave home). I am using MQTT for most of my triggers.
Finally, I have an &amp;ldquo;Alarm Noise&amp;rdquo; HomeKit node, this is a StatelessProgrammableSwitch which is set in the Home.</description></item></channel></rss>