<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tadeusz Wyrzykowski on</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/contributors/shaquu/</link><description>Recent content in Tadeusz Wyrzykowski on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 22:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nrchkb.github.io/contributors/shaquu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Contribution</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/discover-more/contribution/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/discover-more/contribution/</guid><description>Editing Open desired page For example https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/service/lock-mechanism/ Click Edit this page on GitHub
on the bottom of the page You will be directed to the raw page file in our GitHub repository In GitHub editor, add or edit content after last --- For content, you can use markdown (preferred) or html Create new branch for commit and create Pull Request Our Moderators will respond shortly!</description></item><item><title>Service Node</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/nodes/service-node/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/nodes/service-node/</guid><description>This node represents Service in HomeKit. When hosted behind the Bridge it will also represent Accessory.
Configuration Below you can find the list of configurable parameters for Service Node (this Node can also be found as a homekit node or homekit-service).
Service Hierarchy Choose if this node will represent Parent (or Primary) Service or Linked one.
Option Description Parent Node will be used as Primary Service.</description></item><item><title>Status Node</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/nodes/status-node/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 18:51:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/nodes/status-node/</guid><description>This node outputs status of the HomeKit Service.
Configuration Below you can find the list of configurable parameters for Service Node (this Node can also be found as a homekit node or homekit-service).
Service Node Select Service node from the list of already configured nodes which will be used in this node to return status.
Input There is no input payload required. Input port is just used to trigger status output.</description></item><item><title>Roadmap</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/discover-more/roadmap/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 21:21:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/discover-more/roadmap/</guid><description>Here is a list of some things that have been accomplished over the last year or so. Also, a few ideas that have been discussed. Please see the issues' area to discuss and make new requests.
Current efforts: Characteristics properties as GUI option in node configuration Add compatibility for custom characteristics (as requested) Explore possibility of 2-way audio for cameras (discussion here) Potential next developments: Add compatibility with Eve Energy (as requested) Add support to manage other homebridged accessories (made outside the node-red?</description></item><item><title>Changelog</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/discover-more/changelog/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 18:47:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/discover-more/changelog/</guid><description>⚠️ CAUTION ⚠️ Before upgrading make sure that you are using the latest version of Node-RED and latest LTS version of Node.js Upgrading from versions 0.X to 1.X is a breaking change, all devices will be reset in the Home app. Please review the release notes thoroughly before updating! All notable changes to this project will be documented in this file.
The format is based on Keep a Changelog, and this project adheres to Semantic Versioning.</description></item><item><title>Credits</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/discover-more/credits/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/discover-more/credits/</guid><description>This is a place where we would like to thank those who have come before to build the work that we have added to.
History 7 November 2016 Marius Schmeding (@mschm) made the first version of the Node-RED plugin using HAP-NodeJS called node-red-contrib-homekit
13 April 2018 Oliver Rahner (@oliverrahner) steps in and makes a fork called node-red-contrib-homekit-bridged
As Marius Schmeding seems to have abandoned his great work, I decided to fork his repo and to introduce some major rework.</description></item><item><title>FAQ</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/faq/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/faq/</guid><description>How to update NRCHKB node New version has been released, and you would like to upgrade? There are at least two ways to do that!
Using palette In node-red UI click Manage palette in Menu Locate node-red-contrib-homekit-bridged and click update to 1.4.0 Manually Stop node-red cd ~/.node-red npm i node-red-contrib-homekit-bridged@1.4.0 Start node-red Device paired but Service disappearing in Home.app from time to time You managed to pair with Accessory or Bridge but after a while it has disappeared?</description></item><item><title>Release 1.4.0 🥳</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/blog/release-1.4.0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 16:04:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nrchkb.github.io/blog/release-1.4.0/</guid><description>You can read here to find out how to upgrade to the newest version.
Huge thanks to all contributors and testers from our NRCHKB community! Specially to @crxporter and @kevinkub.
Changelog Fixed Fixed customCharacteristics incorrect refresh in UI Implemented static accessoryUUIDs for subflows Enables the use of nrchkb nodes in subflows with backwards compatibility #393 - thanks @kevinkub Fixed Custom MDNS Configuration not showing in UI for Standalone Accessory Stop components from clearing other component&amp;rsquo;s node.</description></item><item><title>Switch</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/service/switch/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2021 18:50:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/service/switch/</guid><description>Switch allow for implementing on/off logic to your devices.
Examples These examples are meant to be copied into your Node-RED system and adapted to your setup.
Simple on/off Switch This is an example of a switch item. The input nodes are &amp;ldquo;On&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Off&amp;rdquo;. The debug node will return values when the switch is turned on or off via the Home app on an Apple device.
Home.app node-red YouTube Copyable Node-RED flow: Click to expand!</description></item></channel></rss>