<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tadeusz Wyrzykowski on</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/contributors/shaquu/</link><description>Recent content in Tadeusz Wyrzykowski on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 22:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nrchkb.github.io/contributors/shaquu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Contribution</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/discover-more/contribution/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/discover-more/contribution/</guid><description>We are open for all contributions regarding our wiki page at https://nrchkb.github.io/
If you want to contribute consider opening discussion first before creating PR.
Structure At content/wiki you will find folders for our wiki sub categories. Introduction General how to pages and articles not fitting rest of categories.
Examples Node-RED examples (working or semi-working flows) that can be used by new users to start a journey with nrchkb.
Service and Characteristic HomeKit&amp;rsquo;s services and characteristics can be found here.</description></item><item><title>Roadmap</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/discover-more/roadmap/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 21:21:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/discover-more/roadmap/</guid><description>Here is a list of some things that have been accomplished over the last year or so. Also, a few ideas that have been discussed. Please see the issues' area to discuss and make new requests.
Current efforts: Characteristics properties as GUI option in node configuration Add compatibility for custom characteristics (as requested) Explore possibility of 2-way audio for cameras (discussion here) Potential next developments: Add compatibility with Eve Energy (as requested) Add support to manage other homebridged accesories (made outside of the node-red?</description></item><item><title>Switch</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/service/switch/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2021 18:50:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/service/switch/</guid><description>Switch allow for implementing on/off logic to your devices.
Examples These examples are meant to be copied into your Node-RED system and adapted to your setup.
Simple on/off Switch This is an example of a switch item. The input nodes are &amp;ldquo;On&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Off&amp;rdquo;. The debug node will return values when the switch is turned on or off via the Home app on an Apple device.
Home.app node-red YouTube Copyable Node-RED flow: Click to expand!</description></item></channel></rss>