<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tadeusz Wyrzykowski on</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/contributors/shaquu/</link><description>Recent content in Tadeusz Wyrzykowski on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 22:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nrchkb.github.io/contributors/shaquu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Demo Setup</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/examples/demo-setup/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/examples/demo-setup/</guid><description>Explanation The nature of this plugin and HomeKit in general is very complex. In the past we have tried screenshots, videos, and other ways to show how things work. With this new demo setup, we are taking it to a new level. You can simply copy the code and paste it right into your Node-RED setup to begin playing with many (eventually all) available HomeKit accessories.
Prerequisites You must have Node-RED and node-red-contrib-homekit-bridged (aka &amp;ldquo;our plugin&amp;rdquo;) installed on your system.</description></item><item><title>ESP</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/examples/esp/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 18:28:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/examples/esp/</guid><description>What is an ESP? ESP is a microcontroller integrated circuit with Wi-Fi connection and very inexpensive. There are several versions of ESP, including ESP32, which is the latest version. ESP32 is more powerful and integrates Bluetooth connection. A popular option is Itead Sonoff modules which integrate an ESP, but the original firmware is not fully &amp;ldquo;open&amp;rdquo; so it cannot be easily added to systems like Node-RED. To solve this problem, ESP Easy or Tasmota firmware can be used to transform the ESP module into a simple multi-function sensor device for home automation solutions.</description></item><item><title>Contribution</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/discover-more/contribution/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/discover-more/contribution/</guid><description>Editing Open desired page For example https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/service/lock-mechanism/ Click Edit this page on GitHub
on the bottom of the page You will be directed to the raw page file in our GitHub repository In GitHub editor, add or edit content after last --- For content, you can use markdown (preferred) or html Create new branch for commit and create Pull Request Our Moderators will respond shortly!</description></item><item><title>Quick Start</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/quick-start/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/quick-start/</guid><description>This wiki will be used to share examples so that users may see how this plugin functions and to get started more easily with copyable flows for each HomeKit service. This page will assume you are familiar with Node-RED basics.
For new users, please start with the official Node-RED docs before continuing.
Nodes A Node is the basic building block of a flow. Nodes are triggered by either receiving a message from the previous node in a flow or by waiting for some external event, such as state change of the light or some automated logic.</description></item><item><title>How to Update</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/how-to-update/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 20:51:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/how-to-update/</guid><description>A new version has been released, and you would like to upgrade? There are at least two ways to do that!
Inside Node-RED In the Node-RED UI, click on the menu at the top right. Go to Manage Palette. Research node-red-contrib-homekit-bridged and click Update. Manually Stop node-red cd ~/.node-red npm i node-red-contrib-homekit-bridged@latest Start node-red</description></item><item><title>Service Node</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/nodes/service-node/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/nodes/service-node/</guid><description>A Service or Service group (Parent and Linked) is considered like Accessory. You can choose to either link your Accessory to a Bridge or use your Standalone Accessory. The difference is when adding in Home.app: In the case of the Bridge, adding the Bridge adds all Accessory linked to that Bridge and in the case of the Standalone Accessory, you only add itself.
Configuration You will find below a table showing all the parameters and when they are used, as well as the list of parameters and their usefulness.</description></item><item><title>Troubleshooting</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/troubleshooting/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 20:51:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/troubleshooting/</guid><description>Device paired but Service disappearing in Home.app from time to time You managed to pair with Accessory or Bridge but after a while, it has disappeared?
Make sure that the device you are using to view Home status is connected to the same network that node-red (with nrchkb) is running on If you are using VLAN or special firewall rules, join us on Discord to discuss what settings should be for things to work Type already defined error Type already defined or Cannot register type errors appeared in UI?</description></item><item><title>FAQ</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/faq/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 20:51:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/faq/</guid><description>How to check software versions How to check versions for most common install methods:
Our node Settings/Manage palette package.json file in your Node-RED installation folder usually ~/.node-red Node-RED Check in the drop-down menu in the top right of the editor.
Node-JS Run node -v in the command line
Which format for msg.payload (JSON) Payload messages sent and received from the HomeKit node have a JSON structure.</description></item><item><title>Status Node</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/nodes/status-node/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 18:51:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/nodes/status-node/</guid><description>This node outputs status of the HomeKit Service.
Configuration Below you can find the list of configurable parameters for Service Node (this Node can also be found as a homekit node or homekit-service).
Service Node Select Service node from the list of already configured nodes which will be used in this node to return status.
Input There is no input payload required. Input port is just used to trigger status output.</description></item><item><title>Washing Machine Monitor</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/examples/washing-machine-monitor/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/examples/washing-machine-monitor/</guid><description>This is a Washing Machine in use flow I created to monitor the usage of our washing machine, and provide notification to the Home.app of the wash status. To create this I leveraged an ESP8266 based current sensor WemosEM to monitor usage of the Washing Machine. And used the flow to determine if the Washing machine was in use, then trigger a Contact sensor.
The flow watches the watts used, averaging the previous 24 readings, and if they cross 30 watts, trigger the On state, and if the average drops below 15 watts trigger the off state.</description></item></channel></rss>