<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Introduction on</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/</link><description>Recent content in Introduction on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Quick Start</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/quick-start/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/quick-start/</guid><description>This wiki will be used to share examples so that users may see how this plugin functions and get started more easily with copyable flows for each HomeKit service. This page will assume you are familiar with Node-RED basics.
For new users, please start with the official Node-RED docs before continuing.
Nodes A Node is the basic building block of a flow. Nodes are triggered by either receiving a message from the previous node in a flow, or by waiting for some external event, such as change state of the light or some automated logic.</description></item><item><title>Service Node</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/service-node/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/service-node/</guid><description>Properties Below you can find the list of configurable parameters for Service Node (you can also find as a homekit node or homekit-service).
Service Hierarchy Service Parent Service This field is only available when Service Hierarchy is set to Linked
Host Type Accessory This field is only available when Service Hierarchy is set to Parent and Host Type is set to Accessory
You can select already created Standalone Accessory Node or create a new one.</description></item><item><title>Host Node</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/host-node/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/host-node/</guid><description>Host Node is either Bridge or Standalone Accessory</description></item><item><title>Output Messages</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/output-messages/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/output-messages/</guid><description>Starting with version 1.3.0, there are some changes in the hap part of the messages coming from this node.
Previous versions would have msg.hap.newValue and msg.hap.oldValue only if the message originated from the Home App. Additionally there was a message part msg.hap.context with some information that nobody really knows what it means, but it was there.
From version 1.3.0 on, the parts of the message will always include msg.hap.newValue and msg.</description></item><item><title>FAQ</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/faq/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/faq/</guid><description>Device paired but Service disappearing in Home.app from time to time You managed to pair with Accessory or Bridge but after a while it has disappeared?
Make sure that device you are using to view Home status is connected to the same network that node-red (with nrchkb) is running on If you are using VLAN or special firewall rules, join us on Discord to discuss what settings should be for things to work</description></item><item><title>Characteristics</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/characteristics/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/characteristics/</guid><description>Characteristics are the values sent to the service item. They are generally true/false or number values. All services have at least one required characteristic. For example the switch has only the required characteristic of On.
Characteristic Properties The HomeKit service node has a section called &amp;ldquo;Characteristic Properties&amp;rdquo;. This section is used to define limits or initialize which characteristics you may send to your specific item.
The characteristic properties do not set any value in the item, instead they tell HomeKit that the item will be using that characteristic and define limits on the valid values.</description></item></channel></rss>