<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Introduction on</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/</link><description>Recent content in Introduction on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 11:54:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Quick Start</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/quick-start/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 11:54:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/quick-start/</guid><description>This wiki will be used to share examples so that users may see how this plugin functions and to get started more easily with copyable flows for each HomeKit service. This page will assume you are familiar with Node-RED basics.
For new users, please start with the official Node-RED docs before continuing.
Nodes A Node is the basic building block of a flow. Nodes are triggered by either receiving a message from the previous node in a flow or by waiting for some external event, such as state change of the light or some automated logic.</description></item><item><title>How to Update</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/how-to-update/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 15:27:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/how-to-update/</guid><description>A new version has been released, and you would like to upgrade? There are at least two ways to do that!
Inside Node-RED In the Node-RED UI, click on the menu at the top right. Go to Manage Palette. Research node-red-contrib-homekit-bridged and click Update. Manually Stop node-red cd ~/.node-red npm i node-red-contrib-homekit-bridged@latest Start node-red</description></item><item><title>Troubleshooting</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/troubleshooting/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 15:27:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/troubleshooting/</guid><description>Device paired but Service disappearing in Home.app from time to time You managed to pair with Accessory or Bridge but after a while, it has disappeared?
Make sure that the device you are using to view Home status is connected to the same network that node-red (with nrchkb) is running on If you are using VLAN or special firewall rules, join us on Discord to discuss what settings should be for things to work Type already defined error Type already defined or Cannot register type errors appeared in UI?</description></item><item><title>FAQ</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/faq/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 18:17:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/faq/</guid><description>How to check software versions How to check versions for most common install methods:
Our node Settings/Manage palette package.json file in your Node-RED installation folder usually ~/.node-red Node-RED Check in the drop-down menu in the top right of the editor.
Node-JS Run node -v in the command line
Which format for msg.payload (JSON) Payload messages sent and received from the HomeKit node have a JSON structure.</description></item></channel></rss>