<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Introduction on</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/</link><description>Recent content in Introduction on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Quick Start</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/quick-start/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/quick-start/</guid><description>This wiki will be used to share examples so that users may see how this plugin functions and get started more easily with copyable flows for each HomeKit service. This page will assume you are familiar with Node-RED basics.
For new users, please start with the official Node-RED docs before continuing.
Nodes A Node is the basic building block of a flow. Nodes are triggered by either receiving a message from the previous node in a flow, or by waiting for some external event, such as change state of the light or some automated logic.</description></item><item><title>Output Messages</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/output-messages/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/output-messages/</guid><description>Starting with version 1.3.0, there are some changes in the hap part of the messages coming from this node.
Previous versions would have msg.hap.newValue and msg.hap.oldValue only if the message originated from the Home.app. Additionally there was a message part msg.hap.context with some information that nobody really knows what it means, but it was there.
From version 1.3.0 on, the parts of the message will always include msg.hap.newValue and msg.hap.oldValue. If the message originated from the Home.</description></item><item><title>Characteristics</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/characteristics/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/characteristics/</guid><description>Characteristics are the values sent to the service item. They are generally true/false or number values. All services have at least one required characteristic. For example the switch has only the required characteristic of On.
Characteristic Properties The HomeKit service node has a section called &amp;ldquo;Characteristic Properties&amp;rdquo;. This section is used to define limits or initialize which characteristics you may send to your specific item.
The characteristic properties do not set any value in the item, instead they tell HomeKit that the item will be using that characteristic and define limits on the valid values.</description></item><item><title>Wait For Setup</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/wait-for-setup/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/wait-for-setup/</guid><description>Wait For Setup feature allows to perform actual accessory configuration in bridge on incoming Setup Message.
Setup Message structure is:
{ &amp;#34;nrchkb&amp;#34;: { &amp;#34;setup&amp;#34;: { ... setup properties goes here } } } In the setup part you may specify properties to configure accessory, such as name, model, manufacturer and other properties available on homekit node.
To configure accessory characteristics setup should contain characteristicProperties string JSON representation for Characteristics Properties as seen in homekit node properties page.</description></item><item><title>FAQ</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/faq/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/faq/</guid><description>How to update NRCHKB node New version has been released, and you would like to upgrade? There are at least two ways to do that!
Using palette In node-red UI click Manage palette in Menu Locate node-red-contrib-homekit-bridged and click update to 1.4.0 Manually Stop node-red cd ~/.node-red npm i node-red-contrib-homekit-bridged@1.4.0 Start node-red Device paired but Service disappearing in Home.app from time to time You managed to pair with Accessory or Bridge but after a while it has disappeared?</description></item></channel></rss>