<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>crxporter on</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/contributors/crxporter/</link><description>Recent content in crxporter on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nrchkb.github.io/contributors/crxporter/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Wait For Setup</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/wait-for-setup/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/introduction/wait-for-setup/</guid><description>Wait For Setup feature allows to perform actual accessory configuration in bridge on incoming Setup Message.
Setup Message structure is:
{ &amp;#34;nrchkb&amp;#34;: { &amp;#34;setup&amp;#34;: { ... setup properties goes here } } } In the setup part you may specify properties to configure accessory, such as name, model, manufacturer and other properties available on homekit node.
To configure accessory characteristics setup should contain characteristicProperties string JSON representation for Characteristics Properties as seen in homekit node properties page.</description></item><item><title>Credits</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/discover-more/credits/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/discover-more/credits/</guid><description>This is a place where would like to thank those who have come before to build the work that we have added to.
Where the Project came from The API work to interact between HomeKit and NodeJS is from HAP-NodeJS.
Marius Schmeding made the first version of the Node-RED plugin to use HAP-NodeJS. His work was later forked by Oliver Rahner who put in a good effort to move over to bridged connections to HomeKit.</description></item><item><title>Valve</title><link>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/service/valve/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2021 18:50:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nrchkb.github.io/wiki/service/valve/</guid><description>Possible Combinations The combination of Active and InUse Characteristics will determine what the Home.app shows for the valve item. Here is a table showing all (known) combinations:
Active InUse Home.app shows 0 0 Off 0 1 Stopping 1 0 Idle 1 1 Running Examples These examples are meant to be copied into your Node-RED system and adapted to your setup.</description></item></channel></rss>